http://www.fruitiongifts.com/privacy.php

Information Collection and Use
Fruitiongifts.com collects information from our shoppers at several different points on our website and in our customer service center, and is the sole owner of this information. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
Order Information
We request information from you on our order form. Here we request you provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as discount purchasing and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of fruitiongifts.com's features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Security
Fruitiongifts.com takes every precaution to protect your information. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, certified by Thawte, which encrypts information you input. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect your information off-line. All of our users¹ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is protected.
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, providing marketing assistance, and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Email Communications
You may choose to receive occasional email communications regarding our site, special offers or services, products or newsletters. We will only send you these emails if you give us permission, and you may choose to stop receiving them at any time.
Notification of Changes
If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our site . If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will not do so without first gaining your permission.
Please contact us at fruit@fruitiongifts.com or call 800-481-3784 with any questions or comments about our privacy policy.
For more information or special requests,email us by clicking here or call toll-free: 800-481-FRUIT (3784)
Click here for our Privacy policy. | Click here for our Site Map. | Click here to view Testimonials.
order Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland onlineorder Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland
online order Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland onlinesend Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Marylandsend
Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland send Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland fresh Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Marylandfresh
Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland fresh Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland 1
2 3
4 5
6 7 8
9 0
1 2 3
4 5
6 7
8 9
gourmet Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Marylandgourmet Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland
gourmet Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore MarylandBaltimore Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore MarylandBaltimore
Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland Baltimore Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore MarylandSunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland
maryland, mdSunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland maryland, md
Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland maryland, md Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland DCSunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland
DC Sunkist Oranges, Clementines Baltimore Maryland DC 1
2 3
4 5
6 7 8
9 0
1 2 3
4 5
6 7
a href="/opt_apples_limes_wholesale_baltimore_maryland_md_dc.php">5
